const QB = [
    {
        "id": "1",
        "question": "Q1) What is the capital of France?",
        "answers": {
            "option1": "London",
            "option2": "Paris",
            "option3": "Berlin",
            "option4": "Tokyo"
        },
        "correctAnswerIndex": 1
    },

    {
        "id": "2",
        "question": "Q2) Which element has the chemical symbol 'O'?",
        "answers": {
            "option1": "Gold",
            "option2": "Oxygen",
            "option3": "Osmium",
            "option4": "Oganesson"
        },
        "correctAnswerIndex": 1
    },

    {
        "id": "3",
        "question": "Q3) Who wrote 'Romeo and Juliet'?",
        "answers": {
            "option1": "Charles Dickens",
            "option2": "Jane Austen",
            "option3": "William Shakespeare",
            "option4": "Leo Tolstoy"
        },
        "correctAnswerIndex": 2
    },

    {
        "id": "4",
        "question": "Q4) What is the smallest prime number?",
        "answers": {
            "option1": "0",
            "option2": "1",
            "option3": "2",
            "option4": "3"
        },
        "correctAnswerIndex": 2
    },

    {
        "id": "5",
        "question": "Q5) Which of the three banks will be merged with the other two to create India’s third-largest bank?",
        "answers": {
            "option1": "Punjab National Bank",
            "option2": "Indian Bank",
            "option3": "Bank of Baroda",
            "option4": "Dena Bank"
        },
        "correctAnswerIndex": 1
    },
    
    {
        "id": "6",
        "question": "Q6) What is the name of the weak zone of the earth’s crust?",
        "answers": {
            "option1": "Seismic ",
            "option2": "Cosmic",
            "option3": "Formic",
            "option4": "Anaemic"
        },
        "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    
    
    
    {
        "id": "7",
        "question": "Q7) Where was India’s first national Museum opened?",
        "answers": {
            "option1": "Delhi",
            "option2": "Hyderabad",
            "option3": "Rajasthan",
            "option4": "Mumbai"
        },
        "correctAnswerIndex": 3
    },
    
    
    {
        "id": "8",
        "question": "Q8) The world’s nation 5G mobile network was launched by which country?",
        "answers": {
            "option1": "Japan",
            "option2": "Asia",
            "option3": "South Korea",
            "option4": "Malaysia"
        },
        "correctAnswerIndex": 2
    },
    
    
    {
        "id": "9",
        "question": "Q9) Vijay Singh (golf player) is from which country?",
        "answers": {
            "option1": "UK",
            "option2": "USA",
            "option3": "India",
            "option4": "Fiji"
        },
        "correctAnswerIndex": 3
    },
    
    
    {
        "id": "10",
        "question": "Q10) The green planet in the solar system is?",
        "answers": {
            "option1": "Mars",
            "option2": "Uranus",
            "option3": "Venus",
            "option4": "Earth"
        },
        "correctAnswerIndex": 1
    },
    

]

export default QB;